spectranet.in 2016-12-22

# Privacy Policy - Spectranet

This website www.spectranet.in (hereinafter referred to as the **"Website"** ) is owned, operated and managed by Citycom Networks Private Limited ( **“Spectranet”** or **“we”** or **“our”** ), a company registered under the provisions of Indian Companies Act, 1956, having its registered office at #A-60 Naraina Industrial Area, Phase -I, New Delhi – 110 028 and corporate office at # 21-22, Phase – IV, Udyog Vihar, Gurgaon – 122015, Haryana and is intended to provide information about the products/services of Spectranet and its group/associate Company which is engaged in providing revolutionary and disruptive Business Internet Access ( **“BIA”** ) products powered by Fiber Optic Xperience ( **“FOX”** ), Data-Centre Products offering metered power, Internet Services, Internet Data Centre, and other value added services which deliver an unfair advantage of abundance to the consumers/end users enabling them to do much more within their budgets. Internet Services, Internet data Centre, and other value added services. Further, in order to demonstrate its commitment to the privacy of users of this Website, we would like to present this site policy.

## Introduction

This Privacy policy describes our policy for collection, use, disclosure, retention, and protection of your personal information from fraud, misuse. It applies to our Website and all its pages and to any of application, service, or tool (collectively the **"Services"** ) where this Privacy Policy is referenced, regardless of how you access or use them, including through mobile or any other devices such as an ipad.

Protecting data is a matter of trust and your privacy is important to us. We shall therefore only use your name and other information, which relates to you, in the manner set forth in this Privacy Policy. We will only collect information where it is necessary for us to do so and we will only collect such information which is relevant to our dealings with you. We will only keep your information for as long as law either requires us to or as is relevant for the purposes for which it was collected.

## User consent to Privacy Policy

Any person accessing, browsing or otherwise using this website located at this website, either manually or via an automated device or program, shall be considered a "User" and is addressed as “User” or “You” in this policy. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to explain the type of information that we collects from you, what we do with that information, and with whom we shares this information

By accessing, browsing or using this Site, you acknowledge that they have read, understand, agree and consent to the Terms and Conditions ( **“T &C”**) of the Policy.Your consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of your information including personal information and anonymous browsing information (collectively the **"Information"** ) pursuant to the terms of this Policy. If you do not consent to these T&C, please do not access, browse, or use this Site If you do not provide the information we require, we may not be able to provide all of our Services to you.

## Collection of Information

The data(s) such as Customer Billing and Personal Profile will be collected using a safe and smooth procedure which is as simple as filing a Customer Application Form ( **“CAF”** ) and all those data(s) will ultimately be stored with our Billing Partner ( **“Third Party”** ) which shall not be disclosed publically as per Rule 6 of the Information Technology (Reasonable Security Practices and Procedures and Sensitive Personal Data or Information) Rules, 2011.

The personal information we collect includes the following information:

  * Information such as your name, mailing address, telephone numbers, email addresses, PAN Card details and other information such as Office address, Installation address
  * Anonymous Browsing Information: Our servers may collect your Internet Protocol address (IP address, your computer's operating system, name of the domain you used to access the Internet, the website you came from and the website you visit next
  * Financial information (such as credit card or bank account numbers) in connection with a transaction, which we do not store at our website as we are using a payment gateway service provider

## Use of Personal Information

We use the personal information we collect from you in our endeavours to serve you in a better way and more particularly: 

  * Transaction Processing
  * Customer Services
  * Personalized Advertising & Marketing
  * To administer contests, survey etc
  * Sending Newsletter/promotional e-mails
  * For detection, prevention, mitigation and investigation of fraudulent or illegal activities

We retain your personal information as long as it is necessary and expedient for our operations. In addition, we may retain personal information from closed accounts to comply with national laws, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigation, enforce our terms of use and take other actions permitted or required by applicable Indian laws. In the event it is no longer required for us to retain your personal information, we dispose it off in a secure manner according to our relevant policies.

## To whom Spectranet shares your information with?

  * If we have your’s consent to share personal information, we may do so.
  * We may provide to others the aggregate statistics about our Users' site activity for purposes of marketing, promotion or similar activities. None of these statistics will identify you personally. 
  * We may disclose Information about our Users to others if we have a good faith belief that we are required or permitted to do so by law or legal process, to respond to claims, or to protect the rights, property or safety of our or others. 
  * In the event that we decides to sell all or part of its assets, we reserves the right to include Information among the assets transferred to the acquiring company.

## Applicable law/ International issues

Information that is submitted to this Site will be collected, processed, stored, disclosed and disposed of in accordance with applicable Indian laws. If you are a Non-Resident India(“NRI”) User, you acknowledge and agree that we may collect and use your Information and disclose it to other entities outside your resident jurisdiction, as discussed in “To whom Spectranet shares your information with?” above. In addition, such Information may be stored on servers located outside your resident jurisdiction. Indian law may not provide the degree of protection for personal information that is available in other countries. By providing us with your Information, you acknowledge that you have read this Policy, understand it, agree to its terms and consent to the transfer of such information outside your resident jurisdiction. If you do not consent to the terms of this Policy and have already provided us with Information, please contact us at [info@spectranet.in](mailto:info@spectranet.in) and let us know how you would like us to handle such Information.

## Linked Internet websites

The Site provides hyperlinks, which are highlighted words or pictures within a hypertext document that, when clicked, take you to another place within the document, to another document altogether, or to other websites not controlled by Spectranet. These hyper linked websites may contain privacy provisions that are different from those provided herein. We are not responsible for the collection, use, or disclosure of information collected through these websites, and Spectranet expressly disclaims any and all liabilities related to such collection, use, or disclosure.

## Security

This Site has security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the Information that is submitted to Spectranet and is under its control. We make no representations or warranties with regard to the sufficiency of these security measures. We shall not be responsible for any actual or consequential damages that result from a lapse in compliance with this Policy as a result of a security breach or technical malfunction. Certain information may be transmitted to you by email. In addition, Users' communications through the Site are, in most cases, viewed only by you and anyone to whom you address your message. As the operator of the Site, we may need to review or monitor your electronic mail and other communications from time to time as may be required by law. Therefore, you should not expect to have a right to privacy in any of your communications.

## Business Transitions

In the event that Spectranet goes through any business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified via a prominent notice on the Web site for 30 days prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information. If as a result of the business transition, the users' personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection they will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section.

## Amendments to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to amend this Policy periodically. Any amendments made to this Policy will be considered effective immediately after the amendments are posted on the Site.

If we decide to change this privacy policy, it will post those changes to this privacy statement and will give notices of the changes on the homepage of the Web Site, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

## How to contact Spectranet?

Any questions or clarifications with respect to this Policy can be sent to Spectranet at: [info@spectranet.in](mailto:info@spectranet.in) or by normal/physical mail addressed to:

__

## Citycom Networks Private Limited

__ **_Corporate Offc:_**

_Citycom Networks Private Limited,  
21-22, Phase – IV, Udyog Vihar,  
Gurgaon – 122015,  
Haryana (India)_
